I feel it stirrin' deep down inside my soul
我听见那灵魂深处的节奏
The rhythm's takin' hold
是节拍在掌控
And it's about to roll
即将席卷四周
A million sparkles falling across the floor
百万点星光闪烁径直坠落
So DJ give it more
请DJ来更多
It's what we're looking for
让全场变热火
Dance the night away
舞~动一整夜
All our friends right by our side
朋友闪耀齐上台
It doesn't matter what style you bring
不管你带~来什么风格
We're about to go on that ride
我们会全部秀出来
It's dance magic
感受旋律
Once you have it
舞出魔力
Let your body move, step into the music
让你的舞步，进入这音乐里
It's dance magic
电音刺激
And it's electric
快舞出魔力
Let your body move to the music
让你的舞步~融合音律
Doesn't matter what style you've got
任何风格都融洽
Just keep dancin' on that spot
只管跳舞最无瑕
Your friends like you for who you are
朋友爱你永不假
Dance queen,on the scene,superstar!
上镜，跳不停，舞蹈家
Crystal Prep, you've got the moves
水晶预科真是酷
Rainboom bringin' all the grooves
虹爆出场皆臣服
Put it together and make it fit
融会贯通在一起
Crystal Rainbooms, dance magic
水晶虹爆，舞出魔力
Dance the night away
舞~动一整夜
All our friends right by our side
朋友闪耀齐上台
It doesn't matter what style you bring
不管你带~来什么风格
We're about to go on that ride
我们会全部秀出来
It's dance magic
感受旋律
Once you have it
舞出魔力
Let your body move
让你的舞步
Step into the music
进入这音乐里
It's dance magic
电音刺激
And it's electric
快舞出魔力
Let your body move to the music
让你的舞步~融合音律
Crystal Rainbooms got a style that's all our own
水晶虹爆风格独特不相同
Dancin' nonstop, body movin' in the zone
脚不停跺，热舞沉浸音乐中
Bring whatever style you've got
任何风格都融洽
'Cause the party is goin' off
让派对狂欢不停下
It's dance magic
电音刺激
And it's electric
快舞出魔力
Let your body move to the music
让你的舞步~融合音律